managemyhome.com 2013-09-26

# Manage My Life - Privacy policy

Effective December 15, 2009:

ManageMyLife.com Privacy Policy

The ManageMyLife Website (formerly known as ManageMyHome.com, hereinafter referred to as "ManageMyLife.com" or "ManageMyLife" or "the Site") wants to ensure that you understand what information we gather about you, how we use it, and the safeguards we have in place in order to protect it. By subscribing to ManageMyLife.com, filling out the forms on the website, or by giving us information while submitting a question or other content to ManageMyLife.com, you consent to the collection, use and sharing of your personally identifiable information, as defined below, in accordance with the our Privacy Policy as well as our Terms of Use.

If you have additional questions or would like further information on this topic, please feel free to write to our Webmaster at [privacy@contact.ManageMyHome.com](mailto:privacy@contact.managemyhome.com).

ManageMyLife may update this policy from time to time. Please check our policy periodically for changes. Your use of ManageMyLife.com, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our Terms of Service and all of its dispute resolution provisions including arbitration, limitation on damages and choice of law.

ManageMyLife.com is a general audience site and does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 18 years of age.

What Type of Information Do We Collect?

ManageMyLife.com collects personally identifiable information from you when you voluntarily submit the information to us in order to register as a member of ManageMyLifecom, when you submit questions, create ToDo lists, or otherwise post content to the site.

Personally identifiable information includes your name, address, telephone number and any other information you voluntarily provide to us which identifies you as an individual. You may choose to additionally provide us with information about your life and your home including the features, market value, product and service purchases and histories related to your home, car or other property. Such information is not considered to be "personal information" when it has been disassociated from you and cannot be easily connected to you. For example, when you submit a question to ManageMyLife.com, we may archive your question and answer for reference by ManageMyLife and by visitors to the Site and other web sites that are part of the Sears Holdings family of businesses. However, any information identifying you as an individual, your address, or your email address or other personally identifiable information ("PII") will have been removed.

ManageMyLife.com may also collect PII from you if you choose to participate in ManageMyLife.com activities like subscribing to our email program, or participating in sweepstakes, contests, and surveys, in connection with content or suggestions you post on the Site, when you submit your personal, family and home information, create "To Do" lists and when you submit questions to the ManageMyLife.com community. You may provide as much or as little information about your life as you like, although the more information you provide, the more useful our services will be.

ManageMyLife.com also collects personal information from the Sears Holdings family of businesses and third party service providers that may have about you or your home. The Sears Holdings family of businesses includes all Sears Holdings affiliates, as well as other selected businesses with which Sears Holdings and its affiliates have a relationship and which have agreed to adhere to our strict standards for providing quality products and services, responding to your needs, and protecting customer information.

ManageMyLife.com also collects information about you and your home, such as its value or mortgages, that may be available via public records.

ManageMyLife.com collects non-personally identifiable information ("non-PPI”, for example: your interests, hobbies, lifestyle choices, groups with whom you are affiliated) from you when you choose to provide or post non-PII information on ManageMyLife.

Non-PII may also be collected from you by means of Cookies and Pixel Tags. Cookies are small bits of information that this web site places on your computer. We and our 3rd party service providers use cookies and Pixel Tags to identify your IP address, browser type, domain name, and specific web pages through which you click. This data is collected automatically and utilized to help us look for trends to improve our web site and your interactive experience. The cookies allow us to recognize you when you return to the Web site and to provide you with a customized experience that we feel will be of value to you. The cookies that are configured by this web site do not contain any personally identifying information, such as your name, or sensitive information, such as your credit card number. Additional information regarding browser cookies and how to disable them is described below.

ManageMyLife.com may also collect additional information about you from third parties including demographic information (such as number of household members, age, and gender) and purchase preference information. We use this information to customize your experience on our web site and on other Sears Holdings family of business web sites and to provide you with the most relevant products, services and offers.

What Information Do We Share and with Whom?

We do not rent or sell your information to outside marketers. We may share your information (as described above) with members of the Sears Holdings family of businesses to provide you with products or services that you have requested or to provide you with promotional offers that we believe will be of interest to you. The Sears Holdings family of businesses includes all Sears Holdings affiliates, as well as other selected businesses with which Sears Holdings or its affiliates have a relationship and which have agreed to adhere to our strict standards for providing quality products and services, responding to your needs, and protecting customer information.

**To Do Lists** — ManageMyLife.com enables you to create and share To Do lists. This feature allows you to create a list of tasks and share it with the ManageMyLife.com community. The To Do List feature is intended to enable you to quickly create and share lists, tasks and details with other members of the ManageMyLife community. You may use this feature to contribute your own lists, tasks and details to ManageMyLife.com's to collective a body of knowledge. By contributing your lists, tasks and details to the community, you enable others to benefit from your knowledge. You may even discover a smarter way to get your own things done. Although the To Do list feature is by default Social in nature and your lists, tasks and details are automatically viewable and searchable by others, we provide you with the option of making individual details, tasks or your entire list of tasks and details private, which prevents others from seeing (and benefiting from) your contributions. Whether public or private, your To Do lists, tasks and details are considered User Generated Content and as such are governed by the [managemylife.com ](http://www.managemylife.com/)Terms of Use, which we encourage you to read.

We also may provide information to regulatory authorities and law enforcement officials in accordance with applicable law or when we otherwise believe in good faith that the law requires it. There may be instances when we may access or disclose your information in order to protect or defend the legal rights or property of Sears Holdings and its affiliated companies or their employees and agents, to protect the safety and security of users and members, and to protect against fraud.

Sears Holdings may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets in connection with a merger, reorganization or sale of assets, or in the event of bankruptcy. In such an event, personal information may be one of the assets transferred.

In certain circumstances, we may share your information with service providers that need access to your information to provide operational or other support services. To ensure the confidentiality and security of your information, service providers must agree to safeguard your information in strict compliance with this policy.

Can I Disable Cookies?

Most web browsers allow you to exercise control over cookie files on your computer by erasing them, blocking them, or notifying you when such a file is stored. Please take a look at your particular browser for instructions on this function. If you do elect to disable cookies, please note that you may not be able to take full advantage of a personalized experience on this Web site and on other Sears Holdings family of business web sites.

How Do We Handle Personally Identifiable Information Collected on Children?

Each Sears Holding's family of Sites that may be directed to children under 13 will contain a specific version of our Children's Online Privacy Policy that will address specifically each of the points listed below for that Site.

  * Collection of children's personal information
  * Use of children's personal information
  * The method of obtaining parental consent
  * The method of obtaining access to the child's information

What About Links to Other Web sites?

This web site may contain links to other web sites outside the Sears Holdings family of web sites. Sears Holdings is not responsible for the privacy practices of other non-affiliated web sites. You should read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.

What About Online Advertisements?

We partner with third-party service providers known as Ad Networks to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet. Using Cookies and Pixel Tags (also known as Web Beacons), Ad Networks collect anonymous information about your visits to our web site and other web sites in order to deliver advertisements that may be of particular interest to you. This process does not involve the collection of any personally identifiable information (PII). The Ad Networks do not know your name, phone number, address, email address or any personally identifying information. If you do not wish to receive relevant ads based on this technology, you can opt-out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative’s (NAI) opt-out page [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

This web site may also carry advertisements from other companies. Sears Holdings and its affiliates are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other companies. Once you click on an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party or advertiser site to determine, among other things, how they will handle any PII they collect from you. These third party advertisements may also contain cookies or web beacons. We do not control these third party cookies or web beacons and you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party or advertiser site to see whether and how it uses cookies or web beacons.

We do not share any personally identifiable information about you with the advertising networks. To find out more about how the networks manage the privacy of information in conjunction with delivering ads online, please go to: <http://www.doubleclick.com/us/corporate/privacy/> or <http://www.atlassolutions.com/privacy2.aspx#atlas_website>. In addition, the Network Advertising Initiative offers useful information about Internet advertising companies; also known as ad networks, including information about how to opt-out of their information collections. See <http://www.networkadvertising.org/participating/> for the list of NAI members and <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp> for the opt-out page.

Is My Information Secure?

We maintain reasonable and appropriate physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your information. Your information is located on a secured server behind a firewall. When you enter PII, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology ("SSL"). While we do work very hard to protect your privacy, no method of security is 100% effective and we cannot be responsible for the actions of those who may gain unauthorized access to your personal information. Sears Holdings makes no warranties, express, implied or otherwise as to the ultimate effectiveness of these reasonable and appropriate safeguards.

How Can I Access My Information?

You can personalize your experience on the Sears Holdings family of web sites by becoming a registered Member. By registering, you will be able to tell us what products and services interest you, and whether you wish to receive e-mail about special sales, promotions and other events. Once registered, you can review and maintain your account information at anytime by logging in and clicking on link with your name or email at the top of each web site page. Your account information is secure and is accessible by using a password that you select. To become a registered member, or to modify your current preferences, go to [www.ManageMyLife.com](http://www.managemylife.com/) and click on the "Login" link.

Can I "Opt-Out" of Receiving Promotional E-mails?

From time to time, we may send you e-mails with promotional offers if you opt-in to receiving such emails. If you would no longer like to receive e-mailed special event information, sales notifications or other promotional messages from this web site, you can unsubscribe from this site’s e-mail marketing list by following the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of each promotional e-mail. Your e-mail address will be removed from this site’s email marketing list within 10 days.

Will I Receive Notice of Changes to the Privacy Policy?

As mentioned above, from time to time we may modify this Privacy Policy to reflect industry initiatives or changes in the law, changes in our collection or use practices, or changes in our web site’s features or technology, and such modifications shall be effective upon posting on this web site. Your continued use of this web site after we post a revised Privacy Policy signifies your acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy. It is therefore important that you review this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure you are updated as to any changes.
